<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="AFP">
    <Package name="Scripts">
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_DisplayName">
            <English>AMM - Operation Ship Plane</English>
            <Polish>AMM - Operacja Statek-Samolot</Polish>
        </Key>

        <!-- MISSION -->
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Mission_Title">
            <English>Operation Ship Plane</English>
            <Polish>Operacja Statek-Samolot</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Mission_Description">
            <English>Scandinavian coalition, composed of Danish, Norwegian and Swedish forces prepares to retake the island occupied by North Korea.</English>
            <Polish>Koalicja skandynawska złożona z Duńczyków, Norwegów i Szwedów przygotowuje się do odbicia wyspy okupowanej przez Koreę Północną.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Mission_ShortDescription">
            <English>Scandinavian coalition, composed of Danish, Norwegian and Swedish forces prepares to retake the island occupied by North Korea.</English>
            <Polish>Koalicja skandynawska złożona z Duńczyków, Norwegów i Szwedów przygotowuje się do odbicia wyspy okupowanej przez Koreę Północną.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Mission_Briefing">
            <English>North Korea invaded Russian island under Danish control in Gulf of Finland. 
No one knows how they managed to get there unnoticed, how they smuggled 3 frigates and an aircraft carrier to Baltic Sea, and even how the hell did they get an aircraft carrier.

Scandinavian coalition, composed of Danish, Norwegian and Swedish forces prepares to retake the island. 
Danes prepared a frigate, a F-16 and an infantry squad, Norwegians added their F-16 and an infantry squad and Swedes fielded 2 Blackhawks and 2 infantry squads. 
Together they will face Hu Ju Son's fleet with the task of retaking the island and finding answers to the questions bothering us.</English>
            <Polish>Korea Północna dokonała inwazji na rosyjską wyspę pod władaniem duńskim w zatoce fińskiej i umieścili tam ważne cele. 
Nie wiadomo jak udało im się tam dostać, jak przemycili na Bałtyk 3 fregaty i lotniskowiec, ani tym bardziej skąd wytrzasnęli lotniskowiec.

Koalicja skandynawska, złożona z Duńczyków, Norwegów i Szwedów zebrała siły i przygotowuje się do operacji odbicia wyspy. 
Duńczycy wystawili fregatę i jednego F-16, Norwegowie dorzucili swojego F-16 oraz drużynę piechoty, a Szwedzi Blackhawka i 2 drużyny piechoty. 
Razem stawią czoła flocie Hu Ju Sona z zadaniem odbicia wyspy oraz znalezienia odpowiedzi na nurtujące nas pytania.</Key>

        <!-- TASKS -->

        <!-- NAVY -->
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Navy_Title">
            <English>Neutralize Hu Ju Son's fleet</English>
            <Polish>Zneutralizuj flotę Hu Ju Sona</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Navy_Description">
            <English>Hu Ju Son's fleet consists of 3 frigates and an aircraft carrier. 
We will not be able to destroy the aircraft carrier but we can, and even must destroy the frigates.</English>
            <Polish>W skład floty Hu Ju Sona wchodzą 3 fregaty i lotniskowiec. 
Lotniskowca nie damy rady zniszczyć, ale fregaty już można, a nawet trzeba.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AircraftCarrier_Title">
            <English>Neutralize the aircraft carrier</English>
            <Polish>Zneutralizuj lotniskowiec</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AircraftCarrier_Description">
            <English>Unfortunately we will not be able to destroy it, probably we will need to board it. 
Maybe we will come up with something during the mission.</English>
            <Polish>Niestety nie damy rady go zniszczyć, prawdopodobnie będziemy zmuszeni go przejąć poprzez abordaż.
Może jednak w trakcie misji uda nam się coś wymyślić.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Frigates_Title">
            <English>Sink frigates</English>
            <Polish>Zatop fregaty</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Frigates_Description">
            <English>Sinking the frigates is crucial to mission's success. 
Otherwise we will not be able to reach the main island and we will need to cancel the mission to avoid extensive casualties.</English>
            <Polish>Zatopienie fregat jest kluczowe dla powodzenia misji.
W przeciwnym razie nie będziemy w stanie przebić się na główną wyspę i będziemy musieli odwołać misję, żeby uniknąć olbrzymich strat.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Frigate_Title">
            <English>Sink frigate</English>
            <Polish>Zatop fregatę</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Frigate_Description">
            <English>Each frigate is armed with artillery cannon, antiship cruise missiles, anti air missiles and C-RAM minigun. 
Destroying enemy frigate will be easier if they focus on our frigate and our air assets tries to bomb them.</English>
            <Polish>Każda fregata uzbrojona jest w działo artyleryjskie, przeciwokrętowe pociski manewrujące, rakiety przeciwlotnicze oraz działko przeciwlotnicze C-RAM.
Zniszczenie fregaty będzie prostsze jeżeli nasza fregata skupi na sobie ogień wrogiej, a lotnictwo w tym czasie spróbuje ją zbombardować.</Polish>
        </Key>


        <!-- AIRFIELD -->
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Airfield_Title">
            <English>Capture the airfield</English>
            <Polish>Zajmij lotnisko</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Airfield_Description">
            <English>First task is to capture the airfield, which will be our field base during the operation. 
Watch out, there may be enemy AA on the airfield.</English>
            <Polish>Pierwszym celem jest zajęcie lotniska, które stanowić będzie naszą bazę wypadową podczas operacji na głównej wyspie.
Uwaga, na lotnisku może znajdować się broń przeciwlotnicza.</Polish>
        </Key>

        <!-- ANTI SHIP BATTERY -->
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AntiShipBattery_Title">
            <English>Eliminate anti ship defense</English>
            <Polish>Zlikwiduj obronę przeciwokrętową</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AntiShipBattery_Description">
            <English>Destroying it will allow our frigate to operate freely on nearby waters.</English>
            <Polish>Umożliwi to sojuszniczej fregacie swobodne operowanie na wodach wokół głównej wyspy.</Polish>
        </Key>

        <!-- COMMS -->
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Comms_Title">
            <English>Destroy the comms tower.</English>
            <Polish>Zniszcz wieżę komunikacyjną.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Comms_Description">
            <English>Destroying this comms tower will make enemy unable to contact the main island and warn them about the invasion.</English>
            <Polish>Zniszczenie tej wieży uniemożliwi przeciwnikowi powiadomienie reszty sił o ataku.</Polish>
        </Key>


        <!-- ISLAND -->
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Island_Title">
            <English>Neutralize enemy forces on the island.</English>
            <Polish>Zneutralizuj siły przeciwnika na wyspie</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Island_Description">
            <English>Koreans set up their anti air and anti ship defense on neighboring island. 
It makes our navy and air force to operate. 
It must be neutralized ASAP.</English>
            <Polish>Koreańczycy umieścili swoją obronę przeciwlotniczą i przeciwokrętową na sąsiedniej wyspie.
Uniemożliwia ona operowanie naszemu lotnictwu i marynarce.
Należy ją jak najszybciej zneutralizować.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_IslandAntiAirWeapons_Title">
            <English>Eliminate AA defense</English>
            <Polish>Zlikwiduj obronę przeciwlotniczą</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_IslandAntiAirWeapons_Description">
            <English>It will enable our air assets to operate freely in airspace west of the main island.</English>
            <Polish>Umożliwi to sojuszniczemu lotnictwu swobodne operowanie w przestrzeni powietrznej na zachodzie głównej wyspy.</Polish>
        </Key>

        <!-- AIRFIELD HQ -->
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AirfieldHQ_Title">
            <English>Set up a field base at the airfield (optional)</English>
            <Polish>Załóż bazę polową na lotnisku (opcjonalne)</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AirfieldHQ_Description">
            <English>We can set up a field base at the airfield.</English>
            <Polish>Na lotnisku możemy założyć bazę polową.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AirfieldFieldHospital_Title">
            <English>Set up a field hospital (optional)</English>
            <Polish>Załóż szpital polowy (opcjonalne)</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AirfieldFieldHospital_Description">
            <English>Field hospital will allow us to heal our men faster and will provide us with additional medical supplies. To build it we need 2 boxes of medical supplies.</English>
            <Polish>Szpital umożliwi nam szybsze leczenie rannych oraz zapewni dodatkowe zapasy medyczne. By go zbudować potrzebujemy 2 kartonów medycznych.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AirfieldServiceDepot_Title">
            <English>Set up a service point (optional)</English>
            <Polish>Załóż punkt serwisowy (opcjonalne)</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AirfieldServiceDepot_Description">
            <English>Service point will allow us to repair and rearm our vehicles. To build it we need a big box and a one barrels pallet.</English>
            <Polish>Punkt serwisowy umożliwi nam naprawę i przezbrojenie pojazdów. By go zbudować potrzebujemy pudła i beczek.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AirfieldInfantryArmory_Title">
            <English>Set up an armory (optional)</English>
            <Polish>Załóż zbrojownię (opcjonalne)</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_AirfieldInfantryArmory_Description">
            <English>Armory will provide the ammunition for infantry. To build it we need brown boxes.</English>
            <Polish>Zbrojownia dostarczy nam amunicji na piechoty. by ją zbudować potrzebujemy brązowych kartonów.</Polish>
        </Key>

        <!-- MAIN ISLAND -->
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_FindImportantTargets_Title">
            <English>Locate important targets</English>
            <Polish>Znajdź ważne cele</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_FindImportantTargets_Description">
            <English>Koreans placed important targets on the main island. They need to be located and secured, not destroyed.</English>
            <Polish>Koreańczycy umieścili na głównej wyspie ważne cele. Trzeba je znaleźć i postąpić odpowiednio, tj. zabezpieczyć, nie niszczyć.</Polish>
        </Key>

        <!-- ARTIFACTS -->
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Artifacts_Title">
            <English>Locate the artifacts</English>
            <Polish>Znajdź artefakty</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Artifacts_Description">
            <English>Airfield intel tells about presence of 3 priceless artifact on the island. Probably this is why Koreans came here. Find them and deliver them to the field base, leave in the marked area.</English>
            <Polish>Intel na lotnisku wskazuje na obecność 3 bezcennych artefaktów na wyspie. Być może po to przybyli tu koreańczycy. Znajdźcie je i przywieźcie do bazy polowej, zostawcie w oznaczonej strefie.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_CingDzban_Title">
            <English>Cing jug</English>
            <Polish>Cing Dzban</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_CingMiska_Title">
            <English>Cing bowl</English>
            <Polish>Cing Miska</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_CingFajkaWodna_Title">
            <English>Cing water pipe</English>
            <Polish>Cing Fajka Wodna</Polish>
        </Key>


        <!-- EVAC -->
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Evac_Title">
            <English>Evacuation</English>
            <Polish>Ewakuacja</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFP_Scripts_Task_Evac_Description">
            <English>Return to base.</English>
            <Polish>Powrót do bazy.</Polish>
        </Key>

    </Package>
</Project>

<!--
    Legacy stuff
-->

<Project name="ArmaForces">
    <Package name="Preset">
        <Key ID="STR_ArmaForces_Preset_DisplayName">
            <English>ArmaForces - Preset</English>
            <Polish>ArmaForces - Preset</Polish>
        </Key>
        <!-- COMMON -->
        <Key ID="STR_ArmaForces_Preset_Dialog_Close">
            <Original>Close</Original>
            <English>Close</English>
            <Polish>Zamknij</Polish>
        </Key>
        <!-- GROUP RENAME -->
        <Key ID="STR_ArmaForces_Preset_Dialog_GroupRename_Rename">
            <Original>Rename</Original>
            <English>Rename</English>
            <Polish>Zmień nazwę</Polish>
        </Key>
        <!-- VIEW DISTANCE -->
        <Key ID="STR_ArmaForces_Preset_Dialog_ViewDistance_Custom">
            <Original>Custom</Original>
            <English>Custom</English>
            <Polish>Ustaw własną</Polish>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
